Kelenson, Milton Papers 5962
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Milton Kelenson Papers
1940-1950
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kelenson, Milton
5962
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
Includes material on discrimination in government.
5743723
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 08, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 18, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Kelenson was a union rep for Local 30, United Public Workers-CIO, and for Local 1, United Federal Workers.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5653: United Federal Workers Records 5962 P: Milton Kelenson Photographs
Kelenson, Milton.
5743723
- PBA Mechanics, 1945-1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Leaflets - Publicity (Box 1, Folder 2)
- United Federal Workers of America, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Discrimination, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Appendix 48, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Plays (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Local 3, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Auxiliary, 1948-1951 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Correspondence Answered, 1948-1950 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- UFWA Publications, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Stewards Mailing, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Transcript of Proceedings - Discrimination case against Bureau of Engraving/Printing, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- United Public Workers of America - "The fight against Documentation", 1946 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Discrimination case, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Engraving & Printing, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- History - Labor & American Democratic, 1944-1954 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Promotion Policy & American Democratic, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Scope and Contents
  7 Photographs
- E&P Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- E&P Promotions, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Agency Rulings on Leave Regulations, 1951-1954 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Efficiency Ratings Material - 1946 Program (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Housing - Branch File, 1947-1951 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Originals, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- 50th Anniversary of Social Security, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Photographs, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  10+ Photographs
- Photographs (Folder 2) (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Photographs (folder 3) (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Photographs (folder 4), 1937 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Photographs (folder 5) (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Photographs (folder 6), 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Photographs (Folder 7) (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Photographs (folder 8) (Box 1, Folder 32)
  10 Photographs
- Photographs (Folder 9) (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Photographs (folder 10) (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Photographs (Folder 11), 1938 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Photographs (folder 12) (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Photographs (folder 13) (Box 1, Folder 37)
  5+ Photographs
- Photographs (folder 14) (Box 1, Folder 38)